socialmedia-forum.com 2009-11-05

# Privacy Policy

We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors; this policy sets out how we will treat your personal information.

(1) What information do we collect?

We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal data:

[(a) information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website (including [your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and number of page views]);

[(b) information relating to any transactions carried out between you and us on or in relation to this website, including information relating to any purchases you make of our goods or services (including conference passes, conference documentation and sponsorships).

[(c) information that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us (including conference passes, conference documentation and sponsorships).

[(d) information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our website services, email notifications and/or newsletters.

[(e) any other information that you choose to send to us.

(3) Using your personal data

Personal data submitted on this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website.

We may use your personal information to:

[(a) administer the website.

[(b) improve your browsing experience by personalising the website.

[(c) enable your use of the services available on the website.

[(d) send to you goods purchased via the website, and supply to you services purchased via the website.

[(e) send statements and invoices to you, and collect payments from you.

[(f) send you general (non-marketing) commercial communications.

[(g) send you email notifications which you have specifically requested.

[(h) send to you [our newsletter and other] marketing communications relating to our business [or the businesses of carefully-selected third parties] which we think may be of interest to you by post or, where you have specifically agreed to this, by email or similar technology (you can inform us at any time if you no longer require marketing communications).

[(i) provide third parties with statistical information about our users – but this information will not be used to identify any individual user.

[(j) deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the website.

Where you submit personal information for publication on our website, we will publish and otherwise use that information in accordance with the license you grant to us.

We will not without your express consent provide your personal information to any third parties for the purpose of direct marketing

All our website financial transactions are handled through our payment services provider, Optimal.  You should only provide your personal information to Optimal after reviewing the Optimal privacy policy (available at [www.optimalpayments.co.uk](http://www.optimalpayments.co.uk/)).  We will share information with  Optimal only to the extent necessary for the purposes of processing payments you make via our website.

(4)  Disclosures

We may disclose information about you to [any of our employees, officers, agents, suppliers or subcontractors] insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes as set out in this privacy policy.

In addition, we may disclose information about you:

(a) to the extent that we are required to do so by law;

(b) in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;

(c) in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk); and

(d) to the purchaser (or prospective purchaser) of any business or asset which we are (or are contemplating) selling.

Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties.

[(5) International data transfers

Information that we collect may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which we operate in order to enable us to use the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

If you are in the European Economic Area (EEA), information which you provide may be transferred to countries [(including [the United States], [Japan], [China] which do not have data protection laws equivalent to those in force in the EEA.

In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the internet and may be available, via the internet, around the world.

You expressly agree to such transfers of personal information.

(6) Security of your personal data

We will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

We will store all the personal information you provide on our secure (password- and firewall- protected) servers. All electronic transactions you make to or receive from us will be encrypted.

Of course, data transmission over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet.

(7) Policy amendments

We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website.  You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes. 

(8) Your rights

You may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you.  Provision of such information may be subject to the payment of a fee (currently fixed at £10.00).

You may instruct us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes by email  at any time.  (In practice, you will usually either expressly agree in advance to our use of your personal data for marketing purposes, or we will provide you with an opportunity to opt-out of the use of your personal data for marketing purposes.)

(9) Third party websites

The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites.

(10) Updating information

Please let us know if the personal information which we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated.

(11)  Contact

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal data, please write to us by email to [ian@sixdegs.com](mailto:mark@sixdegs.com)   or by post to Six Degrees Events Ltd. Top Floor Rear, 25-26 Berkeley Square, Bristol, BS8 1HP.

(12) Data controller

The data controller responsible for our website is Six Degrees Events Ltd. Top Floor Rear, 25-26 Berkeley Square, Bristol, BS8 1HP. 

This website privacy policy is based on a template  
created by [Template-contracts.co.uk](http://www.template-contracts.co.uk/)   
and distributed by [Website-law.co.uk](http://www.website-law.co.uk/)
